Oscar Gonzalez

Tech Lead & iOS developer

More than 4 years of personal experience working with mobile applications & disruptive technologies, developing proof of concepts, prototypes and final applications. Versatile, agile, with knowledge of Project Management, Architecture and Business Processes. Creative person, ready to learn and always hungry for new challenges!

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

2016 present

TECH LEAD & iOS DEVELOPER

BLUE IT - QARACTER

Work in multidisciplinary teams to define, design, and ship new products & features Establish a technical vision to the team and work with developers to turn it into reality Work with project managers and software architects to achieve the best solutions

Design, build and maintain mobile & web applications as its delivery process Implementation and Integration of RESTful APIs & back-end services Continuously discover, evaluate, and implement new technologies

20014 - 2016 2 years

JUNIOR IOS DEVELOPER (INTERNSHIP STUDENT)

ZURICH INNOVATION LAB - TECHNOLOGY DELIVÉRY CENTER (Zurich Insurance Group)

Design, develop and maintain iOS (mobile) & web applications Implementation and Integration of RESTful APIs & back-end services Design and implementation of NoSQL Databases (MongoDB) Help driving innovation and new ideas through the company Continuously discover, evaluate, and implement new technologies (including IoT, Wearables, Drones, Augmented Reality & Big Data)

2012 - 2014 2 years

IT SERVICES SUPPORT / HELPDESK

ANOIA-VALLES

Network infrastructure, servers & desktop setup Support & Manage business applications Software & Hardware issues support

2008 - 2011 5 years MECHANIC, TELEMETRIST & COACH of RACING DRIVERS

KARTBAN & GENIKART

Mechanical setups, telemetric data analysis $\boldsymbol{\Xi}$ driver coaching

EDUCATION

2010 - 2016

UPC - BARCELONA SCHOOL OF INFORMATICS (FIB)

BACHELOR DEGREE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE (Software Engineering)

2008 - 2010

IES SANT QUIRZE

HIGH SCHOOL - BACCALAUREATE

******* AWARDS / CERTIFICATES

- Distinction With Honors in the Bachelor Degree Final Thesis (Employee centered gamification for project management)
- Efma DMI 2016 Nominees "Best Disruptive Product or Service" (BCN Zurich Innovation Lab & the Spider Sense prototype)
- First Certificate in English (FCE) (B2)



III CONTACT DETAILS

Website: ogonzalezadell.me

Fmail:

ogonzalezadell@gmail.com

Mobile:

+34 674 014 584

Social:

@ogonzalezadell

₩ PROFESSIONAL SKILLS



III TECHNOLOGIES

iOS SDK, Objective C & Swift Core Data & Offline storage Push Notifications RESTFul Services Angular, Node & Javscript Android SDK & Java Git & Atlassian suite

₩ LANGUAGES

SPANISH	(native)
ENGLISH	(B ₂)
CATALAN	(native)